dreamcenter.org 2019-03-20

# Dream Center - Privacy Policy

This is the Web site of The Dream Center

**Last updated: October 2, 2017**

Dreamcenter.org knows you care how information regarding you is shared and used, and we are grateful for your trust that we will do so cautiously and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy.

By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you follow any links to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

**Collection of Information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by our visitors. The information you provide is used to fulfill your specific request. This information is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

**Cookie/Tracking Technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

We also use tracking technology for Remarketing and Google Display Network Impression Reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.

**Commitment to Data Security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

**Privacy Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

**Phone:**  [(213) 273-7000](tel:2132737000)  
**Email:**  [marketing@dreamcenter.org](mailto:marketing@dreamcenter.org)

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
